Kirsty Leanne: So, this happened some years ago. I was 19,
and that summer I ended a relationship with my boyfriend.
I wanted to travel as far away as possible, but I needed to get a job!
I was lucky to find temporary work as a receptionist in California,
so I booked my flights with a travel agent. I was really excited.
A few weeks later, just five days before my flight,
I checked all my travel documents.
Suddenly, I noticed a mistake.
My name on the flight booking was Leanna, L-E-A-N-N-A, not Leanne, L-E-A-N-N-E.
Just one small typo, but a very big mistake, because of course,
the name on my ID was Leanne, and I was sure that was a problem.
I immediately called the travel agent and asked them to change the name on the ticket.
They weren’t stressed at all and suggested a solution.
“Don’t worry. We can cancel your ticket and then book you a new one for the same flight.”
It was expensive, but I decided to do it.
When I arrived at the check-in desk,
I showed my ID to the assistant, but my name wasn’t on the flight! I started to panic.
I called the travel agent, and they discovered that it was their mistake.
They talked to the woman at the check-in.
I waited…and I waited… Finally, she handed me my boarding pass.
I was on the flight!
She even arranged transportation for me to get through security quickly, and to my gate.
I was the last person to board the plane,
but when I was in my seat, I finally started to relax.
At last, I was on the biggest adventure of my life!
And the trip ended well – to my great surprise,
when I arrived, my suitcase arrived with me!
An absolute miracle!